lolpix.com 2015-12-06

# LOLpix.com Privacy Policy

LOLPix.com does not collect any personal information about its users. Only what a user enters when setting up a forum account. We do not distribute this information or use it in any way. All views expressed in this page are matter of opinion and are usually not to be at all taken seriously. This site is meant for entertainment, not education. We do not control what type of content is on the sites we link to.

Advertisements  
We may have some advertisments on some pages. We do not control what these links point to or what is on the pages. We do not control any aspect of the advertisments.

Linked web sitesÂ   
We provide links to third party sites. Since we do not control these Web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) third party sites.

Children's privacyÂ   
We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems.

Teach kids never to give personal information, unless supervised by a parent or responsible adult. Includes name, address, phone, school, etc.Â   
Know the sites your kids are visiting and which sites are appropriate.Â   
Look for Web site privacy policies. Know how your child's information is treated.Â   
Check out the FTC's site (1) for more tips on protecting children's privacy online.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visitÂ [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

Return to the home page for the latest [Funny Pictures](http://www.lolpix.com/)
